Criminal Justice, School of; Records ua640
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Dean's Historical Day Files, 1963 April-1971 June; 1; 0.50 cubic ft.
  - Day Files, 1965 June-1966 July; 1.4
    - Letter to Prof. Leon Radzinowicz from E. Lumbard, visit to Cambridge, 08/22/1965 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 130)
    - Letter to Dr. Harry Porter from E. Lumbard, 08/31/1965 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 131)
      re SCJ.
    - Letter to Dr. Harry Porter from E. Lumbard, 09/03/1965 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 132)
    - Letter to Samuel B. Gould from Dean O.B. Conaway, re organization of the proposed SCJ, 09/07/1965 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 133)
    - Letter to Eliot Lumbard from Frank J. Remington, re SCJ, 09/14/1965 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 134)
    - Letter to Dr. Evan Collins from Dean O.B. Conaway, Jr., establishment of SCJ, 09/23/1965 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 135)
    - Letter to Prof. Joseph Leese from E. Lumbard, re SCJ, 11/03/1965 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 136)
    - Memo to Files from E. Lumbard, potential candidate for deanship, 11/03/1965 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 137)
    - Letter to Prof. Joseph Leese from E. Lumbard, re SCJ, 11/03/1965 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 138)
    - Memo to Pres. E. Collins from Harold Syrett, re SCJ, 11/05/1965 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 139)
    - Letter to Webb Fiser from E. Lumbard, re shaping of third conference, 11/12/1965 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 140)
    - Letter to Herman Goldstein from E. Lumbard, re search for head of SCJ, 11/19/1965 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 141)
    - Memo to Robert R. Douglass from E. Lumbard, re SCJ, 11/19/1965 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 142)
    - General Overview of Qualifications for Dean, School of Criminology and Criminal Justice, SUNYA, 1965 December (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 143)
    - Letter to Webb Fiser from E. Lumbard, re Bill Brown becoming consultant and screening potential persons for deanship, 12/07/1965 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 144)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from Webb Fiser, preliminary screening of candidates for Dean, 12/14/1965 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 145)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from Joseph Leese, possible qualifications and canvassing of prospective Dean, 12/16/1965 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 146)
    - Letter to Dr. Webb Fiser from E. Lumbard, re news items in National Council on Crime and Delinquency Issue, 12/21/1965 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 147)
    - Letter to Prof. Leon Radzinowicz from E. Lumbard, re study entitled "The Need for Criminology and a Proposal for an Institute of Criminology", 12/21/1965 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 148)
    - Letter to Samuel B. Gould, stress of need for SCJ, 12/22/1965 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 149)
    - General Overview of Qualifications for Dean, School of Criminology and Criminal Justice, SUNY, 1965 September (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 150)
    - Letter to Miss Charlotte Hollander from Joseph Leese, re Overview of Qualifications for Dean, SCJ, 12/22/1965 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 151)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from Webb Fiser, 12/27/1965 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 152)
    - Letter to Webb Fiser from E. Lumbard, 12/30/1965 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 153)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from L. Radzinowicz, 01/01/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 154)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from Webb Fiser, re SCJ, 01/07/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 155)
    - Memo to W. Fiser from E. Lumbard, re Radzinowicz letter, 01/10/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 156)
    - Letter to Dr. Webb Fiser from E. Lumbard, 02/15/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 157)
      re Ford Foundation grant New York Times article "New Way Sought to Teach Rights", 2/21/1966.
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from Webb Fiser, re search for Dean of SCJ, 02/23/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 158)
    - Letter to Joseph Leese, SUNYA from Richard Schwartz, re candidates for deanship of SCJ, 03/01/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 159)
    - Letter to Webb Fiser from E. Lumbard, re search for head of SCJ, 03/02/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 160)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from W. Fiser, re R. Myren's vita, 03/04/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 161)
    - Letter to Webb Fiser from E. Lumbard, re recruitment of R. Myren, 03/08/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 162)
    - Letter to President Evan Collins from Harold Syrett, recruitment of RAM as Dean of SCJ, 3/10/1966Letter to Eliot Lumbard from Webb Fiser, re Deanship, SCJ, 03/17/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 163)
    - Letter to Prof. R. Myren from E. Lumbard, re appointment as Dean of SCJ, 03/18/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 164)
    - Memo to Robert Douglass from E. Lumbard, re Dean for SCJ, 03/18/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 165)
    - Letter to Webb Fiser from E. Lumbard, re advisory committee, 03/21/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 166)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from R. Myren, thank you for letter appointing him as Dean of SCJ, 03/22/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 167)
    - Memo to R. Myren from L. Hebert, re Budget Allocations for 66-67, 04/13/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 168)
    - Summary of Action taken by Board of Trustees of SUNY at meeting, 1966 April 15 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 169)
    - Transcript from Governor Rockefeller's Conference on Crime, held at the Astor Hotel, NYC, 04/21/1966-04/22/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 170)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from L. Radzinowicz, 05/10/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 171)
    - Letter to Prof. L. Radzinowicz, re Governor Rockefeller's Conference on Crime held 4/21-4/22/1966, 05/24/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 172)
    - Letter to R.A. Myren from E. Lumbard, re Oyster Bay Conferences, 05/24/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 173)
    - Letter to Judge Harold Tyler from E. Lumbard, re serving as member of an advisory council to SCJ, 05/24/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 174)
    - Letter to R.A. Myren from C.M. Harlander, 05/25/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 175)
    - Letter to R. Myren from Prof. William Brown, re Correction Program, 06/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 176)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from Samuel Gould, re TIMES article, 06/13/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 177)
    - Memo by Robert R. Douglass from E. Lumbard, re Fourth Oyster Bay Conference on Organized Crime, 06/15/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 178)
    - Letter to Prof. L. Radzinowicz from E. Lumbard, discussions re report on a proposed Institute of Crim. and SCJ, 07/21/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 179)
    - Page from "Bar Bulletin", 22 New York County Lawyer's Association in No. 5 from E. Lumbard, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 180)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from B. John Tutuska, Sheriff of Erie County, re importance of further training programs, 07/24/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 181)
    - STATUS REPORT, School of Criminal Justice, SUNYA by R. Myren, 13 July 1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 182)
    - Memo to Dr. Webb Fiser from R.A. Myren, re Legal Education for SUNYA, 07/15/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 183)
    - Memo to Robert Douglass from E. Lumbard, re meeting with Dr. Gould, 07/18/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 184)
    - Letter to Samuel B. Gould from E. Lumbard, 07/18/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 185)
      re discussion of educational needs of the criminal justice community, 7/18/1966.
    - Letter to John B. Tutuska from E. Lumbard, re potential police science course at State University, 07/18/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 186)
    - Memo to Robert R. Douglass from E. Lumbard, re Program for Legal Advisors to Police Departments, 07/19/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 187)
    - Memo to Dr. Webb Fiser from R.A. Myren, re Full-Time Research for the School; conference funds, 07/20/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 188)
    - Draft Proposal by R.A. Myren, re AN ADVISORY COMMITTEE FOR THE SCHOOL OF CRIMINAL JUSTICE OF THE SUNYA, 07/20/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 189)
    - Memo to Webb Fiser from R.A. Myren, 07/21/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 190)
      re Gould-Lumbard-Myren conference of 7/18/66.
  - Day Files, 1966 August-1966 November; 1.5
    - Letter to Richard Braun from R.A. Myren, re info on Criminal Division of U.S. Dept. of Justice, 08/01/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 191)
    - Letter to Robert Fosen from R.A. Myren, note of appreciation for Dr. Fosen's time and discussion of plans for SCJ, 08/01/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 192)
    - Letter to R.A. Myren from Robert Fosen, re visit & developments of SCJ, 08/03/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 193)
    - Letter to R.A. Myren from Richard Braun, 08/04/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 194)
    - Letter to Charles Breitel from C.M. Harlander, re dinner meeting, 08/05/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 195)
    - Report by R.A. Myren, re future of CJ systems, 1966 August (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 196)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from Samuel B. Gould, re discussion of educational needs of the CJ community, 08/05/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 197)
    - Letter to Dr. Bernard Russell from R.A. Myren, re planning meeting, 08/16/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 198)
    - Letter to Richard Braun from R.A. Myren, re planning meeting, 08/16/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 199)
    - Letter to Dr. Robert Fosen from R.A. Myren, re planning meeting to formulate preliminary program for SCJ, 08/16/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 200)
    - Letter to Prof. L. Radzinowicz from E. Lumbard, re dinner meeting of 10/4/1966, 08/23/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 201)
    - Letter to C.M. Harland from Nicholas J. Tonti, re Judge Breitel attending dinner meeting, 08/23/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 202)
    - PROPOSAL FOR THE PROGRAM, MASTER OF SCIENCE IN CRIMINAL JUSTICE, Undated (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 203)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from R.A. Myren, re proposal for SCJ program, 08/26/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 204)
    - Copy of newspaper notice in New York Law Journal of from EHL, 09/16/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 205)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from L. Radzinowicz, 09/04/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 206)
    - Letter to R.A. Myren from E. Lumbard, re dinner meeting, 09/10/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 207)
    - Letter to Samuel Gould from E. Lumbard, re meeting on SCJ, 09/22/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 208)
    - Letter to Robert Douglass from E. Lumbard, re meeting on SCJ, 09/22/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 209)
    - Letter to Professor Herbert Wechsler from E. Lumbard, re meeting on SCJ, 09/22/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 210)
    - Letter to Harold Tyler, from E. Lumbard, re meeting on SCJ, 09/22/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 211)
    - Letter to Prof. L. Radzinowicz from E. Lumbard, re meeting on SCJ, 09/22/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 212)
    - Letter to Clifton Phalen from E. Lumbard, re meeting on SCJ, 09/22/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 213)
    - Letter to Russell Niles from E. Lumbard, re meeting on SCJ, 09/22/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 214)
    - Letter to Richard Myren, from E. Lumbard, re meeting on SCJ, 09/22/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 215)
    - Letter to Charles Breitel from E. Lumbard, re meeting on SCJ, 09/22/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 216)
    - Letter to Prof. Lloyd Ohlin from E. Lumbard, re dinner meeting, 09/26/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 217)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from, Charles Breitel, re dinner meeting, 09/27/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 218)
    - Memo to E. Lumbard from C.M. Harlander, re dinner meeting on SCJ, 09/29/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 219)
    - Letter to President Gould & Mr. Douglass, from E. Lumbard, re dinner meeting re SCJ, 10/04/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 220)
    - Memo re dinner meeting tentatively set for re SCJ, 10/04/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 221)
    - Memo re dinner meeting re SCJ, 10/04/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 222)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from Russell D. Niles, re SCJ, 10/12/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 223)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from Dean R.A. Myren, note of thanks re discussion plans for SCJ, 10/21/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 224)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from Dean R.A. Myren, re dinner w/NYC Bar representatives and Oyster Bay Conference, 10/21/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 225)
    - Letter to Judge Breitel from E. Lumbard, meetings re SCJ, 10/24/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 226)
    - Letter to Prof. Herbert Wechsler from E. Lumbard, 10/24/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 227)
    - Letter to Russell Niles from Eliot Lumbard, meetings re SCJ, 10/24/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 228)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from L. Radzinowicz, 10/24/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 229)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from Charles Breitel, planning meetings for SCJ, 10/26/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 230)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from Russell Niles, 10/27/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 231)
    - Memo to Files from Eliot Lumbard, re SCJ, 10/31/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 232)
  - Day Files, 1966 November-1967 August; 1.6
    - A STATUS REPORT, School of Criminal Justice, SUNY, by Richard A. Myren, 1966 November (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 233)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from Herbert Wechsler, 11/02/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 234)
    - Memo to President Evan Collins from R. Myren, 11/10/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 235)
      re NYC Criminal Justice Dinner, 12/6/1966.
    - Memo to R. Myren from Webb Fiser, re Social Science Field Laboratories for SUNYA, 11/11/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 236)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from Evan Collins, 11/17/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 237)
    - Letter to Evan Collins from Russell Niles, 11/29/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 238)
    - Letter to Evan Collins from E. Lumbard, 11/29/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 239)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from R. Myren, re status report on SCJ, 11/30/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 240)
    - Visiting Committee for the SCJ, SUNYA, 12/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 241)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from Charles Breitel, 12/01/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 242)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from Evan R. Collins, discussion of SCJ, 12/15/1966 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 243)
    - Memo to Faculty, SUNYA from Eugene McLaren, University Senate Sub-Committee on Faculty Research, 01/06/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 244)
    - Visiting Committee for the School of Criminal Justice of SUNYA, Statement of Purpose, etc., 01/16/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 245)
    - First Meeting of Committee of Three, Tentative Plans - RAM, 02/03/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 246)
    - Letter to L. Radzinowicz from E. Lumbard, 02/08/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 247)
    - Letter to R. Myren from E. Lumbard, re Advisory Committee Members, 02/08/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 248)
    - Newspaper clipping from Knickerbocker News, "State U. Names Emrich to Post" -- Assistant Dean, SCJ, 02/09/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 249)
    - Memo to R. Myren from Mary C. Farrington, re Budget for the Law Component for the library of SCJ, 02/14/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 250)
    - Letter to R. Myren from E. Lumbard, re Advisory Council, 02/15/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 251)
    - Letter to R. Emrich from E. Lumbard, re appt as Assistant Dean, 02/21/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 252)
    - FELLOWSHIPS AND ASSISTANTS, School of Graduate Studies, 02/01/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 253)
    - Memo to E. Flinton from R. Myren, re Graduate Fellowship stipends, 02/24/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 254)
    - BUILDING A LIBRARY COLLECTION TO SUPPORT THE PROGRAMS OF SCJ, 02/27/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 255)
    - PLANNING MEMORANDUM 67-1, SCJ, SUNYA, 02/27/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 256)
    - Letter from L. Radzinowicz, re SCJ proposal, 04/03/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 257)
    - Memo to R. Myren, from Elmer C. Matthews, re Summer Budget, 04/06/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 258)
    - PLANNING MEMORANDUM, 67-2, SCJ SUNYA, News and Notes, 04/25/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 259)
    - Letter to R. Myren from Donald Riddle, John Jay College of Criminal Justice, re reactions to planning proposal, 05/15/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 260)
    - Memo to all Deans and Dept. Chairmen from Webb Fiser, re Budget request for 1968-69, 05/16/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 261)
    - Letter to Evan Collins from E. Lumbard, acceptance to appointment to visiting committee, 05/16/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 262)
    - Letter to R. Myren from Al Cohen, reactions to planning memorandum 67-2, 05/18/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 263)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from R. Myren, re Visiting Committee, 05/22/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 264)
    - Letter to R. Myren from Hans Toch, re proposal for SCJ, 05/24/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 265)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from R. Myren, 05/24/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 266)
    - Memo to Webb Fiser from R. Myren, 05/25/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 267)
      re Budget Request for 1968-1969, Budget Code, 48031; Account Title, Crim. Jst.
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from R. Myren, re Visiting Committee, 05/29/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 268)
    - Letter to R. Myren from J. Ll. J. Edwards, re Ph.D. in CJ proposal, 06/06/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 269)
    - Requirements for 1968-69 budget, 06/06/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 270)
    - Note to the File from R. Myren, Summary of previous student and faculty projections, 06/08/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 271)
    - Charter Members, Visiting Committee, SCJ, SUNYA, Undated (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 272)
    - Memo to Webb Fiser from R. Myren, re Six-Year Budget Projection for SCJ, 06/12/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 273)
    - SUNYA, SCJ, Six-Year Budget Projection (1968-69 to 1973-74) Underlying Assumptions, 06/13/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 274)
    - Memo to Webb Fiser, Robert A. Stierer, from R. Myren, re Six Year Budget Projection: Underlying Assumptions, 06/14/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 275)
    - PLANNING MEMORANDUM 67-3, School of Criminal Justice, STATE UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK AT ALBANY, NEWS AND NOTES, 06/19/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 276)
    - Letter to R. Myren from Hans Toch, reaction to draft of program proposals, 06/30/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 277)
    - Letter to R. Myren from A. Cohen, re comments on programs for SCJ, 07/10/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 278)
    - Letter to R. Myren from "Bill", re Doctoral Program memo - responses to three questions, 07/12/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 279)
    - Memo to Faculty from Jim Munro, re Research Planning Memorandum 1, 07/25/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 280)
    - Letter to R. Myren from Jim Munro, re settling in Albany, 07/25/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 281)
    - Memo to Deans of Schools from Webb Fiser, re 1968-69 Budget, 08/02/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 282)
    - Memo to Profs. Wm. Brown, Fred Cohen, Jim Munro, Don Newman, Hans Toch from R. Myren, re Budget for 1968-69, 08/11/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 283)
    - Memo to Jim Munro from Bill Brown, re Research Planning Memorandum 1, 08/17/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 284)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from R. Myren, re Visiting Committee, 08/30/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 285)
  - Day Files, 1967 September-1968 March; 1.7
    - A PROPOSAL FOR THE PROGRAMS, DOCTOR OF PHILOSOPHY - Ph.D. (Criminal Justice) MASTER OF PHILOSOPHY - Ph.M (Criminal Justice), MASTER OF ARTS - M.A. (Criminal Justice), SCJ, 1967 September (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 286)
    - A PROPOSAL FOR THE PROGRAM, DOCTOR OF PHILOSOPHY IN CRIMINAL JUSTICE, SCJ, 1967 September (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 287)
    - Resume of William P. Brown, 09/1967? (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 288)
    - Visiting Committee Prospects, R. Myren, 01/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 289)
    - Notes to File - Fiscal 1968-69 from R. Myren, Undated (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 290)
    - Release from U.S. News and World Report on Albany Campus "Something New in College Campuses", 09/04/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 291)
    - Memo to deans, Div. Chairmen, Dept. Chairmen from Webb Fiser, re Professional Salary Schedule for 1967-68, 09/13/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 292)
    - Memo to Faculty, Farrington, Feit from R. Myren, re Post-Doctoral Fellows, 09/17/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 293)
    - Letter to R. Myren from E. Lumbard, re Visiting Committee, 09/19/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 294)
    - Memo to Deans of Colleges and Schools, Dept. Chairman from Wm. Seymour, re Employment of Visiting Faculty - 1968 Summer Session, 09/29/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 295)
    - Memo to Deans of Schools and Colleges, Dept. Chairman from Wm. Seymour, re Guidelines for Planning the 1968 Summer Sessions, 09/29/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 296)